Md Farhad

House #3, Road #8, Block #E, Section 12, Mirpur, Dhaka | 01960-918062 | farhad45203@gmail.com | https://github.com/farhad45203



OBJECTIVE

I'm a front end developer (React.js & Next.js) with a focus on creating (and occasionally designing) exceptional digital experiences that are fast, accessible, visually appealing, and responsive. Even though I have been creating web applications for over 3+ years, I still love it as if it was something new.

COMPUTER SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Wordpress, React js and Next js etc.

EXPERIENCES

Dates 2020 - Present	Front End Web Developer, SOCIAN LIMITED The development of the front end depends on the project of the company.
Dates	Data Entry Operator, SOCIAN LIMITED
2018 - 2020	Data processing, data analysis and data management according to the needs of the company.
Educations	
Dates	Bachelor of Social Science, Dhaka Mirpur.
Running	Govt. Bangabandhu College.
Dates	Bachelor of Social Science, Dhaka Mirpur.
2018 - 2020	Govt. Bangabandhu College.
PROJECTS DETAILS	

https://farhad45203.github.io/md-farhad/ Md Farhad

> This is my portfolio website. where I showcase all my details and contact information. Also showcases my other project examples and details with gitHub code links.